Subindex build by Linnet
孩子们 在2012年的夏天
Kids,in the spring of 2012,
Barney叔叔消失了几个星期
your Uncle Barney went off the grid for a couple weeks.
所以他发短信让我去他家的时候 我感觉松了口气
So I was relieved when I got a text asking me to come over to his place.
你终于联系我了 我一直担心你是不是
Glad to hear from you,buddy. I was worried something bad happened...
出了什么问题
...to you.
- 欢迎 兄弟 - 这是在唱哪出?
- Welcome,brother. - What is this?
Ted Evelyn Mosby 你要承诺保守秘密
Ted Evelyn Mosby,you are about to be sworn to secrecy
在神圣的兄弟契约的见证之下 也就是兄约
through the sacred vows of a Bro Oath,or "Broath.
请穿上你的兄袍
" Please,put on your "brobe.
我才不要穿什么兄袍
" Yeah,I'm not putting on the "brobe.
Ted 你就穿一下下啦
" Ted,just... just... Okay?
这歌声是在唱"兄弟"吗?
Wait,are they chanting "bro"?
我请一些修道士录的
I got some local monks to record this.
我连修道士都认识 很厉害吧?
Yeah! I got a monk guy. Cool,right?
确实
It actually is,yeah.
我给你刻一张盘 宣完誓之后提醒我
I'll burn it for you. Just remind me after The Broath.
言归正传 Ted Evelyn Mosby
Anyway,Ted Evelyn Mosby,
这个仪式是为了让你 保守一个庄严的秘密
this ritual forever binds you to keep a solemn secret...
- 什么秘密? - 我真的很喜欢Quinn!
- Which is? - I really like this Quinn girl!
我们已经交往一段时间了 我想把她正式介绍给你们认识
We've been spending tons of time together,and I want the gang to meet her.
但是我怕你们不同意 因为你懂的
but I'm afraid they're gonna disapprove because,well,you know.
我的确知道
I did know.
Quinn是个脱衣舞娘
You see,Quinn was a stripper...
还坑了Barney一大笔钱
who had swindled Barney out of quite a bit of cash.
我们想请所有人去Quinn家吃饭
We're inviting everyone to dinner at Quinn's,
我不想大家对她有成见 所以请跟我宣读兄约
and I want them to keep an open mind,which brings us to The Broath.
把手放在兄弟法典上
Place your hand on The Bro Code.
好吧好吧
Yeah,yeah,yeah...
跟着我念 我Ted Evelyn Mosby...
Repeat after me. I,Ted Evelyn Mosby...
我Ted(真不该告诉你我的中间名)Mosby
"I,Ted "Why Did I Ever Tell You My Middle Name" Mosby...
郑重承诺不会告诉其他人 Quinn是脱衣舞娘
" ...solemnly swear not to tell our friends that Quinn is a stripper.
"...solemnly swear not to tell our friends that Quinn is a stripper"
而且还骗了你一大笔钱
who duped you out of lots of money.
你只能重复我的话
You're only supposed to repeat after me.
"You're only supposed to repeat after me.
- 别闹 - 别闹
- Stop it. - Stop it.
安静!
Silence!
虽然我和Quinn刚开始发展得不顺
Look,I know that things started out sketchy with me and Quinn,
但是我真的很喜欢她 所以拜托你
but I really like her,so please.
请问你 Ted(省略中间名)Mosby
Do you,Ted Middle-Name-Omitted Mosby,
愿意发誓遵守这条兄约吗?
swear to uphold this Broath?
我愿意
I do.
Barney在和一个脱衣舞娘交往 结果可能是人财两空
Barney's dating a stripper who's gonna steal all his money!
-=伊甸园美剧论坛http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=- Proudly Presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 食梦貘 福尔摩君 Starcrossed 校对: 葱家的小毛毛 时间轴: 卡灰
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- Sync: 卡灰
老爸老妈浪漫史 第七季 第十九集 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
How.I.Met.Your.Mother S07E19 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
准备去Quinn家了 记住 我什么都没说过
Okay,time to go to Quinn's. Now remember,I told you nothing,okay?
Barney真的希望我们能喜欢她
Barney really wants us all to like her.
怎么可能? Quinn明显是在骗Barney 而且他还浑然不觉
But how can we? Quinn totally duped Barney,and he couldn't even see it.
因为她床上功夫好
Well,apparently,the sex is mind-blowing.
这我有经验
Ha,I've been there. Yeah.
我曾经有个女人 给我开门的时候几乎全裸
I was once with this chick who answered the door wearing nothing
身上只有鲜奶油 项圈领子 和一条性感粉红丁字裤
but,uh,whipped cream,a dog collar and a hot pink thong.
Marshall 你不能讲这些三俗故事
Marshall,you can't tell sex stories about "this chick,"
因为所有人都知道那是我
because everyone knows it's me.
你这辈子就我一个女人
I'm the only woman you've ever been with.
这不公平 别的男人都能讲三俗故事
It's not fair,the guys are always telling their sex stories
何况我的故事绝对能秒杀他们
and I can top every one of them.
老婆 你就是20个风情万种 性感女郎的集合
Baby,you're like 20 slutty chicks all rolled into one.
甜言蜜语也哄不了我
Sweet talk is not going to change my mind.
说正事
Let's focus.
今晚 我们要确认Quinn 是不是在骗Barney的钱
Tonight,we want to make sure that Quinn is not out to scam Barney.
所以三个小时之后 当我们回来的时候
So,when we walk back through that door three hours from now,
都必须明白一个简单的问题
we should all be able to answer one simple question:
3个小时之后
3***
这姑娘可靠吗?
Do we trust this girl?
至少 她能镇得住Barney
Well,for one thing,she seems kind of controlling.
现在把豆泥拿来吃行吗 亲爱的?
Is it okay if I put out the hummus,bunny face?
不行 留着当甜点 白痴
No,save it for dessert. Idiot.
又要续杯了 大美女?
More red wine,beauty-swan?
她真能喝啊
She drinks a lot.
我能去上厕所吗 小乖乖?
Is it okay if I go pee,sugar lamb?
不行 你三小时前刚上过了
No! You just went three hours ago.
你说得对 小甜心!
You're right,baby bear!
Barney确实很听话 但那也不代表Quinn是个骗子
Yes,so Barney's whipped; it doesn't mean that Quinn is a con artist.
也许我们能对她了解多一点
Well,maybe we could've gotten a better read on her
如果某两位不跑偏题的话
if two people hadn't gone off topic.
Quinn 你这公寓真漂亮
By the way,Quinn,your apartment is amazing.
- 是啊 很漂亮 - 我快搬家了
Oh,yeah,it's beautiful. I'm actually moving out soon.
正想找人转租出去 这房子租金受管制
If you know anyone looking for a sublet,this place is rent-controlled.
你们肯定不相信我房租多少钱
You would not believe what I pay.
孩子们 这段时间我和Robin 的关系有些紧张
Kids,things have been tense between Robin and I for weeks.
自从她搬走之后 我把公寓给了Marshall和Lily
Ever since she moved out,and I gave the apartment to Marshall and Lily,
我一直住在大学宿舍
I'd been crashing in university housing.
已经10点呢
It's 10:00,damn it.
Ned Martin和Millie 我要睡觉了好么
Ned,Martin and Millie,people are trying to sleep!
你也曾经年轻过吧?
Hey,you were young like us once,right?
我从来不像你们
I was never like you guys.
Robin和她的同事Patrice住在一起
And Robin was staying with her coworker,Patrice.
你今天好像不高兴 Robin 我给你做了些曲奇
You seem so down today,Robin. I made you cookies.
天哪 Patrice 你想逼死我吗!
Damn it,Patrice,stop smothering me!
所以当Quinn说她的公寓招租时
So,when Quinn said her apartment was available...
- 我要!我要!我要! - 我抢!我抢!我抢!
- It's mine! It's mine! It's mine! - Dibs! Dibs! Dibs!
我们偏题了? 那Marshall呢?
We got off topic? What about Marshall?
我只是按照某人的建议在玩游戏
Hey,I was just going along with whoever suggested we play that game.
我们来玩个游戏吧!
Hey,let's play a game!
最疯狂的公共场所三俗故事 我先开头
Uh,craziest sex-in-public story; I'll start.
有个姑娘喜欢在电梯里搞搞
I was once with this chick who loved to get freaky in elevators.
电梯门一关 她突然趴下来 就像一只发热的小狗
Doors would close; suddenly,she's panting on all fours like a dog in heat.
- Marshall 别说了 - 我又没说是你
- Marshall,stop. - I never said that it was you.
去年八月  我和这姑娘来了次不戴套的
Okay,so anyway,last August,I go bareback with this same slut.
她虽然怀孕了 可以比以前更饥渴了
She get's pregnant; bitch is even hornier.
我曾经搞过一个人 做的时候在吃三明治
Oh,yeah? I was once with this dude who I caught eating a sandwich during sex.
肉丸子掉到我背上 滚到电梯地上
Big ol' meatball falls out,lands on my back,rolls on to the elevator floor.
很恶心是吧?
Hmm. Disgusting,right?
怎么 我又没说是你
What,I never said it was you.
抱歉我们没你们那么集中精力
Yeah,sorry we didn't stay as laser-focused as you guys.
至少我发现了证据
Hey,at least I got some evidence.
看我在Quinn卧室里发现了什么 Barney要带她去夏威夷
Look what I found in Quinn's bedroom. Barney's taking her to Hawaii.
Lily 你翻人家东西了?
Lily,you snooped through her stuff?
没有 第一眼就看到了
No. It's like the first thing you see
就像Jimmy日记里写的
when you jimmy open her desk drawer with a letter opener her grandfather left her,
用她爷爷留给她的开信刀 撬开桌子抽屉就行了
according to her diary.
头等舱机票 四星级酒店 Barney肯定花了不少钱
First-class tickets,a four-star hotel-- this cost Barney a fortune.
这表示Quinn完全是为了钱在利用他
Yeah,this proves that Quinn is totally using him for his money.
Lily 别闹了
You know what Lily,enough.
就算Quinn是这种人 但这是Barney
Guys,even if you're right about Quinn,this is Barney.
他总会想明白的 顶多花一个星期 最多两个星期
He'll come to his senses. I give this whole thing a week,two weeks,tops.
- 现在我们要宣布一件事 - 我来说吗?
- And now,we have an announcement. - Can I tell them?
- 不行 我们要搬到一起住了 - 我们...
- No. We're moving in together - We're m...
恭喜 太好了 真替你们高兴
- Congrats! - That's great. - So happy for you.
必须解决这个事
We gotta end this.
对
Yup.
孩子们 你们应该记得
Kids,as you'll recall,
当我们其中一人快犯错误时 有一个小传统来解决问题
our gang had a subtle way of letting someone know they were making a mistake.
劝说会
intervention
你去哪儿了?
Where have you been?
正经事 等等
Oh,worth it. Hang on.
Quinn说会
quin***
我们确实很烦人是吧?
You know we would've hated ourselves,right?
Robin告诉你们她今天所做的 见不得人的事儿了吗?
So,did Robin tell you the incredibly devious thing she did today?
我?!
Me?!
我正好路过
Hey,so I just happened to be in the neighborhood
我忽然想到 上帝啊 Quinn的身材 好到爆 绝对喜欢水果
and I thought,"Man,Quinn is in such great shape,she must love fruit.
虽然有点儿不相关 但找到买家了吗?
" So,unrelated,how's the search for a sub-letter going?
这真是个奇妙的巧合啊!
This is such a weird coincidence!
Robin也"刚好路过"
Robin also "just happened" to be in the neighborhood
带着一瓶酒和信用评分
with a bottle of wine and her credit scores.
真不敢相信你们 你们还关心个啥
I can't believe you two. What do you care about more,
不让你朋友受伤 还是争夺她的公寓?
protecting your friend from getting hurt or scoring this girl's apartment?
有个能用的壁炉!
There's a working fireplace!
Patrice根本不会熨我的裤子!
Patrice is ironing my pants all wrong!
你们真丢人
You guys should be ashamed.
说到丢人
Speaking of shame,
我曾经跟个小妞儿在一起 她喜欢在夹克下面手淫
I was once with this chick who liked to do hand stuff underneath a jacket
当我们在MacLaren的最喜欢的位子 聚会的时候
while we were all sitting around our favorite booth at MacLaren's.
- 真恶心 - 我们一起吃开胃菜
- Gross. - We share appetizers.
那好吧 我之前跟个男的一起
Okay,well,I was once with a dude
他甚至无法想象"三人行"
who couldn't even fantasize about a three-way.
- 总是说"她是你最好的朋友" - 现在呢?
- He was all,"Ew,she's your best friend. " - What now?
我曾经跟个女孩儿在一起 她在学校彼特潘排练的时候
I was once with a chick who wanted to get it on
特别想要
during a school production of Peter Pan.
等一下 那不是我
Well,I... Wait,that wasn't me.
好吧回到Patrice和这个熨斗事件
So,back to Patrice and this ironing issue...
我以为我是你的第一个
I thought I was the first girl you ever did anything with.
认真对待的人
Anything serious.
别跟我说你在吃醋
Please don't tell me that you're jealous of me
和十年级的Jenna Cristalli 二次上垒
getting to second base in tenth grade with Jenna Cristalli.
别在孩子面前说那贱人的名字
Don't say that whore's name in front of our baby.
出什么事儿了?
What's going on?
Barney这是次劝说
Barney,this in an intervention.
一次Quinn劝说会
A "Quinntervention.
"你和Quinn进展实在太快了 我们不信任她
" You and Quinn are moving really fast,and we don't trust her.
我们只是为了你好
We're just looking out for your best interests.
Quinn好
"Quinn-terests.
我不明白
" I don't understand. Wh...
等一下 Ted Evelyn Mosby...
Wait a sec. Ted Evelyn Mosby...
你违背了兄弟之约
you broke The Broath.
你怎么敢?!
How dare you?!
兄弟之约是最坚固的
A Broath is the most sacred bond between--
好吧 我说了
okay,yeah,I did.
你知不知道 破坏兄弟之约会带来 致命的后果?
Are you aware that breaking a Broath can have deadly,even fatal repercussions?
你学过历史吗 Ted?
Have you studied history,Ted?
深入学习过 但我对有部分历史 有点儿怀疑...
Extensively. But I'm a little shaky on fake history,so...
违背兄弟之约带来的悲惨代价
The tragic cost of a broken Broath Uh-huh.
回到远古兄弟时代...
dates back to Ancient Bro-man times...
兄弟 你告诉我 如果
Hey,Bro-tus,you'd tell me if,like,
一群人企图刺杀我?
a bunch of dudes were conspiring to assassinate me,right?
当然 凯撒 胡思乱想够了?
Um,totally,Caesar. Paranoid much?
只是为了确定一下 你能跟我 定下兄弟之约吧?
Just to be sure,can you swear a Broath to me?
当然 我发誓
Sure. I swear.
谢谢 你永远都是我的坚强后盾
Thanks. You've always got my back.
兄弟?
Et tu,Bro-te?
然后他上了一百个妞儿  发明了一种沙拉 (有种色拉叫凯撒)
And then he banged,like,a hundred chicks and invented a salad.
真实的故事
True story.
Quinn骗了你 操纵了你
Well,Quinn lied to you; she manipulated you.
- 如果她只是在利用你呢? - 她没有利用我
- What if she's just using you? - She's not just using me.
去夏威夷的昂贵之旅怎么说?
What about the expensive trip to Hawaii?
什么夏威夷昂贵之旅?
What expensive trip to Hawaii?
我为你准备的
The one I got for you.
那应该是给Barney的惊喜
That was supposed to be a surprise for Barney.
他让我来这儿见他
He asked me to meet him here.
伙计 你们在干嘛?
What's going on,you guys?
告诉她
Tell her.
好吧 我来满足她
Fine,I'll fill her in.
我太生气了 甚至没法儿拿满足她 来开玩笑
And I am so angry,I'm not even gonna make a joke about "filling her in.
可我昨晚那么做了三次 自我欢呼
" Which I did three times last night,self-five.
我朋友觉得你不适合我 所以 他们正在进行劝说会
My friends think you're wrong for me,so they're having an intervention.
Quinn劝说会
A "Quinntervention.
我不明白
" I don't understand.
既然你的名字是Quinn所以...
Well,see,your name is Quinn,and so...
我来解释
I'll explain.
我让Ted发誓不告诉他们你的职业
I made Ted promise not to tell them what you do,
可他还是说了 他们现在不信任你
but he did,and now they don't trust you.
那可真伤人
Wow,that really hurts.
更糟的是你觉得你需要对此隐瞒
But what's even worse is that you felt the need to lie about me.
我不以自己为耻 Barney 显然你会
I'm not ashamed of who I am,Barney,but you clearly are.
我不以你为耻 我只是不希望 他们随意评价你
I'm not ashamed of you. I just didn't want them to judge you without...
也许我们进展太快了
Maybe we are moving too fast.
什么?这什么意思?
What? What is that supposed to mean?
我觉得我没法儿这样
I don't think I can do this.
等等 这就是你一贯的结束方式?
Wait,are you ending things just like that?
如果你走出了那扇门 你就证明了 他们是对的
If you walk out that door,you prove them right.
证明了你只是个毫无感情可言的 脱衣舞女郎
You prove that you're just some heartless stripper
从来也没他妈的对我...
who never gave a damn about me in the...
不许给我打电话
Don't call me.
这下真够狠的 (Marshall还想让Lily加上Quinn)
Wow. That was intense.
我们刚刚毁了可能一生一次的幸福
We just destroyed what could have been a once-in-a-lifetime shot at happiness.
我知道 我也很有负罪感
I know. I feel guilty,too.
壁炉 阳台 硬木地板...
Fireplace,balcony,hardwood floors...
好 我就这么说
Okay,I'll just say it:
在经历了我们之间的风风雨雨之后
After everything that happened between us,
我不敢相信你不示弱 还不让我租Quinn的房子
I can't believe you wouldn't back down and let me have Quinn's place.
Ted 我们能出去谈谈吗?
Ted,can I talk to you out in the hall?
你有没有想过过去的几周对我来说 也不容易?
Has it ever occurred to you that the last few weeks haven't been easy for me either?
在一天的时间里 我的婚约取消了
In the span of one day,my engagement fell apart,
我失去了我最好的朋友 然后又失去了公寓
I lost my best friend,then I lost my apartment.
现在我又要丢掉工作
And-and now I'm about to lose my job.
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
我工作完全无法集中精神
I-I've been completely distracted at work.
我老板想在星期五五点见我
And now my boss wants to see me Friday at 5:00,
公司人都知道那是"炒鱿鱼时间"
which,around the office,is known as "fire o'clock."
- 我不知道 - 你怎么会?
- I had no idea. - How could you?
我最想谈谈的人甚至都不看我一眼
The one person I want to talk to most barely looks me in the eye anymore,
不回我电话
much less returns my calls.
Ted我知道让你说爱我不容易
Ted,I know it took guts to tell me you love me.
我知道我没回应你很受伤
And I-I know how much it hurt that I didn't say it back,but...
见鬼 我也很难受
Damn it,th-this sucks for me,too.
我想你了
And I-I miss you.
有什么办法能让我们...
Is there any way we can just...
恢复正常?
go back to normal?
我觉得我们没法儿回到过去了
I don't think I can do normal anymore.
Barney还不回电话 我们得去找他 跟他道歉
Barney still isn't answering. We gotta go find him and apologize.
我以为是Quinn
Oh. I thought you were Quinn.
Barney对不起 我们不该那样插手
Barney,we're so sorry. We never should've meddled like that.
能原谅我们吗?
Can you forgive us?
不知道 你们无权那么做
I don't know. You had no right to do that.
伙计 我们要怎么补偿你?
How can we make it up to you,buddy?
我 Barney的挚友之一
I,one of Barney's best friends...
"我 Barney的挚友之一"
"I,one of Barney's best friends..."
发誓永远不再干涉他的私人生活
... promise never to interfere with his personal life again...
"发誓永远不再干涉他的私人生活"
"...promise never to interfere with his personal life again..."
除非有关健康 国家安全
...unless it's an issue of health,national security,
或者他变胖
or he's about to get up on a fattie.
"除非有关健康 国家安全
"...unless it's an issue of health,national security,
或者他变胖"
or he's about to get up on a fattie."
为了坚固这个誓言 两位女士亲吻
And now,to seal this sacred vow,the two ladies will kiss.
- Barney... - 两位女士亲吻!
- Barney... - The two ladies will kiss!
Lil...好吧
Lil... Okay.
- 现在轮到男士 - 伙计...
- And now the gentlemen. - Dude...
该男士们了!
And now the gentlemen!
我们就...这样也太蠢了
Let's just... This is silly.
别 别捧着我的脸
Don't-don't touch my face.
我本来是要说 "该先生们碰拳了"
I was going to say,"And now the gentlemen bump fists.
你们是憋了多久了?
" How long you been holding back that one?
很劲爆啊 各位
Hot stuff,fellas.
舌头功夫都用上了吧?
Did I see a little tongue in there?
我不明白
I don't understand.
如果这两个家伙能有半秒的时间 不把手放在对方身上我就解释
Well,if these two will keep their sweaty paws off each other for half a second,I'll explain.
一切开始于几天前...
It all started a couple days ago...
我想让你见见我的朋友们
I want you to meet my friends.
我该不该紧张啊?  这是不是相当于见家长了?
Should I be nervous? Is it like bringing me home to meet your parents?
不 不 不 比见家长压力还大
No,no,no. Much more stressful than that.
我的朋友们 虽然人都很好 但有时候也很专横 爱管闲事 破坏力超大
You see,my friends,while awesome,can be presumptuous, meddlesome and downright destructive.
如果他们知道了你的工作 和我们是如何相遇
When they learn what you do and how we met,
他们可能会想办法拆散我们
they'll probably try to break us up.
所以让我们耍耍他们吧
So let's have some fun with them. Mess with their heads.
你是说...邪恶计划?
Are you saying... evil plan?
没错
Hells to the yes.
上帝 你太性感了
My God,you're hot.
等一下
Wait for it.
我们就这么办
Here's what we do.
我先让Ted发誓不告诉任何人你的身份
I'll make Ted swear not to tell anyone what he knows about you,
然后他就会马上崩溃了
and he'll cave immediately.
Barney正在和一个脱衣舞女约会 她会把他的所有钱骗走!
Barney's dating a stripper who's gonna steal all his money!
然后 我们就请所有人来玩儿 我就会一直说这样的话:
Next,we invite everyone over. I'll keep saying stuff like:
我是不是应该 把鹰嘴豆泥拿出来了 娃娃脸?
Is it okay if I put out the hummus,bunny face?
然后我就演一个跋扈的贱人 说:
And I'll be the bossy bitch who says:
不要 留着当甜点 白痴
No,save it for dessert,idiot.
漂亮 最后 我们就宣布...
Nice. And,finally,we'll announce...
我们要同居了!
We're moving in together!
我又有一个主意
I've got an idea.
我们应该让Ted和Robin 为我的公寓争斗不休
Let's get your friends Ted and Robin fighting over my apartment.
等下 这和我们有什么关系?
Wait,what does that have to do with you and me?
没什么关系 我就是喜欢闹剧
Nothing. I just worship chaos.
你太性感了 我受不了了
I can't handle how hot you are right now.
等一下
Wait for it.
接下来 他们肯定会劝我甩了你
Next, they'll try to talk me into dumping you.
- 然后我去撞个正着 - 然后我们就假装要分手
- And I'll walk in on it. - Then we pretend to break up.
然后等他们回来祈求原谅时...
And when they crawl back,begging for forgiveness...
我就当个好人 结束这个闹剧
I'll be the bigger man and let them off the hook.
或者让猴子们为你起舞
Or make the monkeys dance for you.
上帝 你太聪明了!
God,you're smart!
这将会是传...
It's gonna be legen...
我等不了了
I'm not waiting for it anymore.
...奇的
...dary.
我的天啊 你俩真是...
My God,you two are...
天生一对
Perfect together.
所以你们不是真的同居?
So you're not really moving in?
开始的时候是个玩笑来着 但我们越是讨论...
Well,it started out as a joke,but the more we talked about it...
越觉得激动 所以 我们确实同居了
The more excited we got. So,yeah,we are.
你们就没有什么要说的?
You have anything to say about that?
- 真为你们高兴 - 恭喜
- So happy for you. - Congratulations.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们两个知道这意味着 我的公寓真的要出租了 对吧?
You two realize this means my apartment really is up for grabs,right?
我肯定还能找到别的公寓的
I'm sure I'll find something else.
- 我也是 - 好吧
- Me,too. - Yeah.
这就是我们如何遇见Quinn的故事
And that's the story of how we met Quinn.
那个周五 我去见了Robin 问她"解雇时刻"的结果如何
That Friday,I met Robin to see how it went at "fire o'clock.
他们让我升职到直播达人秀了
" They promoted me to on-air talent.
我要成为Sandy Rivers的新主持搭档了
I'm gonna be Sandy Rivers' new co-host.
哦 天啊! 这是怎么回事?
Oh,my God! How'd that happen?
记得新年前夜吗?
Remember New Year's Eve?
我给Sandy代班  结果世界新闻的首席执行官很喜欢我
When I filled in for Sandy,it turns out the C.E.O. of World Wide News liked me.
他说我很有"精力"
He said I have "moxie.
他是四十年代的黑帮成员吗?
" So he's a 1940s gangster?
看来是
Apparently.
我加薪了 所以我租了中央公园西大道的一件公寓
And I got a big raise,so I'm taking this apartment on Central Park West,
- 也就是说... - Quinn的公寓
- which means... - Quinn's apartment.
我已经跟她说你会租了
I already told her you'd take it.
- 谢谢 - 没事
- Wow. Thanks. - Yeah.
恭喜你 这是你应得的
Hey,and congrats. You deserve it all.
你知道吗 我一直在想...
You know,I've been thinking about it,and...
我们可以做普通朋友的
I can do normal.
- 敬回到普通朋友 - 敬回到普通朋友
- To back to normal. - To back to normal.
- 我 我得走了  - 是啊 你有很多事情要做
- I-I should get going. - Yeah. You've got a lot to do.
- 必须的 - 所以...
- Totally. - So...
- 过几天见 - 过几天见 嗯
- Um,see you soon. - See you soon. Yeah.
我们会有很长时间见不到面
We wouldn't see each other for a long time.
但我会习惯的
But I'll get to that.
听着 呃...
Listen,um...
关于我在十年级的时候 跟Jenna Cristalli上了二垒...
about me getting to second base in tenth grade with Jenna Cristalli...
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我已经不记得这个婊子了
I've already forgotten about that dumb hobag.
那次不是发生在 我们一起看彼得潘的时候
Yeah,um,it didn't happen while we were watching Peter Pan.
而是发生在我扮演彼得潘的时候
It happened while I was playing Peter Pan.
这是选角那天的照片
Here's a photo from the day I was cast.
中间那个是我
That's me in the middle.
但是后来我进入了速长期
But then I had my growth spurt.
在开场当晚 我太重了 把钢丝都弄断了...
By opening night,I was too big for the flying harness,and,well...
我手先落下掉在Jenna Cristalli身上
I fell hands-first right onto Jenna Cristalli.
她胸罩里垫的纸巾让我的手腕不至骨折
The tissues in her bra saved me two broken wrists.
对不起 我只是 我只是希望 能有一个很酷但女主不是你的三俗故事
I'm sorry. I just,I just wanted to have one cool sex story that wasn't you.
好吧 下次讲故事的时候 你就说你在你爸的车里
Okay. Next time you tell it,you were in your dad's car,
车是你偷来去看金属乐队演唱会的
which you stole to go to a Metallica concert,
然后你和那个婊子上了三垒
and you got to third base with that slut.
有一次我和一个妞在一起...
I was once with this chick...
这个妞就是我的好老婆
who is just the best wife ever.
谢谢你并不介意我的工作
Thank you for being so cool about what I do.
很多男人都会觉得怪异或者吃醋
A lot of guys would be weird or jealous.
开什么玩笑? 我哪有资格去指责别人?  我就是大魔头!
Are you kidding? Who am I to judge anyone? I'm the devil!
我是说如果你不想跳脱衣舞的话 我会支持你的
I mean,if you ever wanted to stop stripping,I'd support it.
如果你不想...的话
If you wanted... to.
哈 所以说 你还是吃醋了?
Uh-huh. So,you are jealous?
什么? 没 没 没有的事儿
What? No,no,not at all.
我是说如果你哪天想挂G带退休
I'm just saying,if you ever wanted to hang up the ol' G-string,
我绝对理解你
I'd completely understand.
不必了 我挺享受为钱宽衣的感觉
Nah,I like taking my clothes off for money.
很好 等我...等我说完
Great. Let me... let me finish.
假设一下 你怎样才愿意不跳?
Hypothetically,what would make you stop?
假设一下...
Hypothetically...
如果我结婚了 就不跳了
I would stop stripping if I ever got married.
晚安
Good night.
然后我们决定"回到普通朋友"
And then we agreed to "go back to normal.
但是我开始怀疑 我们真的能只做普通朋友吗
" But I'm starting to wonder if we can ever really just be friends.
总之 这就是我和Robin  2005年到现在的故事
Anyway,that's the story of me and Robin,2005 to the present.
你们觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
我觉得你的故事也太长了
I think your stories are way too long.
我替他未来的孩子感到悲哀 老兄
I feel bad for his future kids,dude.
嘿 我的孩子们肯定会爱死我的故事
Hey,my kids are gonna love my stories.
他们会...没错 他们会爱死我的故事
They're gonna... yeah,they're gonna love my stories.
老爸老妈浪漫史 第七季 第十九集 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
How.I.Met.Your.Mother S07E19 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo